MUHAMMAD PANDU AFFANDI

DOCUMENT CONTROLLER | DRAFTER | IT

Serang, Banten, Indonesia | Phone: +62822 4353 3194 | E-Mail pandu.affandi15@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Last degree Bachelor of FITE, Technology University of Yogyakarta majoring in Informatics with +1 year experience. He is familiar with the world around Document Controller, Pipe Isometric Draws and IT including website developer, database, system analyst, UI/UX Design, Computer Security Method. He is a person who is enthusiastic and loyal to the company, able to work in a team or individually, a fast learner and adaptive in a fast-paced environment, willing to learn new things and highly motivated to participate any opportunity.

EXPERIENCE

PT. SUCOFINDO (Persero) – Cilegon, Indonesia

Sept 2022 – Now

Administration UP Suralaya

- Prepair Document, HPL, Drauft Survey from Inspector.
- Release Certification of Weight, Certification of Analysis and Invoices.

PT. SUCOFINDO (Persero) – Cilegon, Indonesia

Sept 2021 – Mar 2022

Drafter

Create pipe isometric drawings from handmade drawings and processed into Microsoft Visio and AutoCAD.

PT. SUCOFINDO (Persero) – Cilegon, Indonesia

Mar 2022 – Apr 2022

Document Controller

- Create reports and process data from the inspector and drafter consisting of UT thickness, photos and isometric drawings.
- Create daily reports and work progress in the field.
- Processing pipe data to be submitted to the user and inspector.

Kanan Vape Store – Serang, Indonesia

Apr 2021 – May 2021

Web Developer

Create, developed and maintenance company profile website.

Pura Raharja Hospital – Yogyakarta, Indonesia (*Internship*)

Jan 2019 – Aug 2019

Web Developer

Create, developed and maintenance an information system for employee admissions using the SAW (Simple Additive Weighting) method.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics – Technology University of Yogyakarta

(2015 - 2020)

Cryptography Implementation System for Security Data Text Using the Rivest Shamir Adleman (RSA) Method. GPA: 3.12/4.00

ORGANIZATION

Secretary – Himpunan Mahasiswa Informatika

Jan - Jun 2017

- Create and archive outgoing mail.
- Summarize meeting notes.
- Coordinate with every internal element of the organization.
- Assist the daily management performance.
- Responsible to the chairman of the association and deputy chairman of the association.

Public Relations – Pengabdian Masyarakat Teknik Informatika UTY

May 2017

Village clean-up activities and distribution of basic necessities

SEMINAR & WORKSHOP

Seminar Mobile Forensics – Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Feb 2020

Law enforcement and forensics application development in the digital age.

3D Design and 2D Motion Graphic – Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Mar 2019

Training and Certification Based on National Work Competency Standards (SKKNI) in the KOMINFO sector for the young workforce 3D Design and 2D Motion Graphic Schemes.

3D Character Design – Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Mar 2019

Competency-Based Training for the young workforce in the field of 3D Character Design expertise.

Pekan Keilmuan – Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Jan 2019

Create and develop technology that can be used in the home (Smart Home).

National Seminar Big Data – Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Dec 2018

Data Mining & Machine Learning on social media as a source of Big Data.

LANGUAGES

English

Bahasa

SKILLS

- Programming (HTML, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, CSS, C++, C#)
- Framework (Laravel Framework and Bootstrap)
- Database (MySQL, Oracle and Microsoft SQL Server)
- Multimedia (Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, Figma, Corel Draw and Blender 3D)
- Microsoft Office (Excel, Power Point, Visio and Word)
- Communication both written or spoken
- Teamwork and Leadership
- Problem Solving